 [
      {
        "question_no.": 1,
        "Question": "Which of the following is NOT a major nutrient group?",
        "Option1": "Carbohydrates",
        "Option2": "Fats",
        "Option3": "Vitamins",
        "Option4": "Fiber",
        "Answer": "Fiber"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 2,
        "Question": "What is the primary role of carbohydrates in the body?",
        "Option1": "Building muscle tissue",
        "Option2": "Providing long-term energy storage",
        "Option3": "Acting as the body's main source of energy",
        "Option4": "Regulating body temperature",
        "Answer": "Acting as the body's main source of energy"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 3,
        "Question": "Which nutrient is essential for growth, repair, and maintenance of body tissues?",
        "Option1": "Carbohydrates",
        "Option2": "Proteins",
        "Option3": "Fats",
        "Option4": "Vitamins",
        "Answer": "Proteins"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 4,
        "Question": "What is the recommended daily intake of water for an average adult?",
        "Option1": "1-2 liters",
        "Option2": "2-3 liters",
        "Option3": "3-4 liters",
        "Option4": "More than 4 liters",
        "Answer": "2-3 liters"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 5,
        "Question": "Which of the following vitamins is fat-soluble?",
        "Option1": "Vitamin C",
        "Option2": "Vitamin B12",
        "Option3": "Vitamin K",
        "Option4": "Folic acid",
        "Answer": "Vitamin K"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 6,
        "Question": "The main function of the digestive system is to:",
        "Option1": "Filter waste products from the blood",
        "Option2": "Break down food into smaller molecules for absorption",
        "Option3": "Produce hormones for body regulation",
        "Option4": "Transport oxygen to the body's cells",
        "Answer": "Break down food into smaller molecules for absorption"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 7,
        "Question": "Digestion of carbohydrates begins in the:",
        "Option1": "Stomach",
        "Option2": "Small intestine",
        "Option3": "Mouth",
        "Option4": "Esophagus",
        "Answer": "Mouth"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 8,
        "Question": "What is the name of the enzyme in saliva that begins the digestion of starches?",
        "Option1": "Pepsin",
        "Option2": "Amylase",
        "Option3": "Lipase",
        "Option4": "Trypsin",
        "Answer": "Amylase"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 9,
        "Question": "The wave-like muscle contractions that move food through the digestive tract are called:",
        "Option1": "Absorption",
        "Option2": "Peristalsis",
        "Option3": "Segmentation",
        "Option4": "Mastication",
        "Answer": "Peristalsis"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 10,
        "Question": "The stomach's lining is protected from its own acid by:",
        "Option1": "Villi",
        "Option2": "Mucus",
        "Option3": "Bile",
        "Option4": "Saliva",
        "Answer": "Mucus"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 11,
        "Question": "Which enzyme in the stomach is responsible for beginning the digestion of proteins?",
        "Option1": "Amylase",
        "Option2": "Lipase",
        "Option3": "Pepsin",
        "Option4": "Trypsin",
        "Answer": "Pepsin"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 12,
        "Question": "The majority of nutrient absorption occurs in the:",
        "Option1": "Stomach",
        "Option2": "Large intestine",
        "Option3": "Small intestine",
        "Option4": "Esophagus",
        "Answer": "Small intestine"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 13,
        "Question": "The finger-like projections that line the small intestine and increase the surface area for absorption are called:",
        "Option1": "Rugae",
        "Option2": "Villi",
        "Option3": "Pyloric sphincters",
        "Option4": "Haustra",
        "Answer": "Villi"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 14,
        "Question": "What is the role of bile in digestion?",
        "Option1": "Digesting proteins",
        "Option2": "Emulsifying fats",
        "Option3": "Absorbing water",
        "Option4": "Breaking down carbohydrates",
        "Answer": "Emulsifying fats"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 15,
        "Question": "Which organ produces bile?",
        "Option1": "Gallbladder",
        "Option2": "Pancreas",
        "Option3": "Stomach",
        "Option4": "Liver",
        "Answer": "Liver"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 16,
        "Question": "The pancreas secretes which of the following digestive enzymes?",
        "Option1": "Pepsin",
        "Option2": "Amylase",
        "Option3": "Lipase",
        "Option4": "All of the above",
        "Answer": "All of the above"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 17,
        "Question": "What is the primary function of the large intestine?",
        "Option1": "Breaking down proteins",
        "Option2": "Absorbing water and electrolytes",
        "Option3": "Digesting fats",
        "Option4": "Producing digestive enzymes",
        "Answer": "Absorbing water and electrolytes"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 18,
        "Question": "Where is undigested food stored before it is eliminated from the body?",
        "Option1": "Small intestine",
        "Option2": "Stomach",
        "Option3": "Rectum",
        "Option4": "Liver",
        "Answer": "Rectum"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 19,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a water-soluble vitamin?",
        "Option1": "Vitamin A",
        "Option2": "Vitamin D",
        "Option3": "Vitamin C",
        "Option4": "Vitamin E",
        "Answer": "Vitamin C"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 20,
        "Question": "What is the function of the gallbladder?",
        "Option1": "Produce bile",
        "Option2": "Store and concentrate bile",
        "Option3": "Produce digestive enzymes",
        "Option4": "Absorb nutrients",
        "Answer": "Store and concentrate bile"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 21,
        "Question": "The breakdown of food by chewing and mixing is a form of:",
        "Option1": "Chemical digestion",
        "Option2": "Mechanical digestion",
        "Option3": "Absorption",
        "Option4": "Elimination",
        "Answer": "Mechanical digestion"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 22,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a key function of proteins?",
        "Option1": "Energy storage",
        "Option2": "Insulation",
        "Option3": "Enzyme and hormone production",
        "Option4": "Primary energy source",
        "Answer": "Enzyme and hormone production"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 23,
        "Question": "Which organ is responsible for detoxifying harmful substances and producing blood proteins?",
        "Option1": "Pancreas",
        "Option2": "Stomach",
        "Option3": "Liver",
        "Option4": "Kidneys",
        "Answer": "Liver"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 24,
        "Question": "The small intestine is divided into three sections. What are they in order?",
        "Option1": "Jejunum, ileum, duodenum",
        "Option2": "Duodenum, jejunum, ileum",
        "Option3": "Ileum, duodenum, jejunum",
        "Option4": "Duodenum, ileum, jejunum",
        "Answer": "Duodenum, jejunum, ileum"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 25,
        "Question": "What is the name of the sphincter that separates the stomach from the small intestine?",
        "Option1": "Cardiac sphincter",
        "Option2": "Pyloric sphincter",
        "Option3": "Anal sphincter",
        "Option4": "Esophageal sphincter",
        "Answer": "Pyloric sphincter"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 26,
        "Question": "The breakdown of food molecules using enzymes is a form of:",
        "Option1": "Mechanical digestion",
        "Option2": "Chemical digestion",
        "Option3": "Absorption",
        "Option4": "Peristalsis",
        "Answer": "Chemical digestion"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 27,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a micronutrient?",
        "Option1": "Carbohydrates",
        "Option2": "Fats",
        "Option3": "Minerals",
        "Option4": "Proteins",
        "Answer": "Minerals"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 28,
        "Question": "What is the main function of the epiglottis?",
        "Option1": "Producing saliva",
        "Option2": "Preventing food from entering the trachea",
        "Option3": "Breaking down starches",
        "Option4": "Storing bile",
        "Answer": "Preventing food from entering the trachea"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 29,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a type of protein that speeds up chemical reactions in the body?",
        "Option1": "Hormones",
        "Option2": "Enzymes",
        "Option3": "Antibodies",
        "Option4": "Collagen",
        "Answer": "Enzymes"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 30,
        "Question": "Where are most of the digestive enzymes produced?",
        "Option1": "Stomach and liver",
        "Option2": "Mouth and esophagus",
        "Option3": "Pancreas and small intestine",
        "Option4": "Gallbladder and large intestine",
        "Answer": "Pancreas and small intestine"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 31,
        "Question": "The process of moving food from the mouth to the stomach is called:",
        "Option1": "Peristalsis",
        "Option2": "Deglutition (swallowing)",
        "Option3": "Mastication",
        "Option4": "Absorption",
        "Answer": "Deglutition (swallowing)"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 32,
        "Question": "What is the function of the hydrochloric acid in the stomach?",
        "Option1": "Neutralizing stomach acid",
        "Option2": "Activating pepsinogen and killing bacteria",
        "Option3": "Emulsifying fats",
        "Option4": "Digesting carbohydrates",
        "Answer": "Activating pepsinogen and killing bacteria"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 33,
        "Question": "Which nutrient provides the highest energy density (calories per gram)?",
        "Option1": "Proteins",
        "Option2": "Carbohydrates",
        "Option3": "Fats",
        "Option4": "Vitamins",
        "Answer": "Fats"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 34,
        "Question": "The end products of carbohydrate digestion are:",
        "Option1": "Amino acids",
        "Option2": "Fatty acids and glycerol",
        "Option3": "Monosaccharides (simple sugars)",
        "Option4": "Nucleotides",
        "Answer": "Monosaccharides (simple sugars)"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 35,
        "Question": "The end products of protein digestion are:",
        "Option1": "Amino acids",
        "Option2": "Fatty acids and glycerol",
        "Option3": "Monosaccharides (simple sugars)",
        "Option4": "Nucleotides",
        "Answer": "Amino acids"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 36,
        "Question": "The end products of fat digestion are:",
        "Option1": "Amino acids",
        "Option2": "Fatty acids and glycerol",
        "Option3": "Monosaccharides (simple sugars)",
        "Option4": "Nucleotides",
        "Answer": "Fatty acids and glycerol"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 37,
        "Question": "What is the name of the semi-liquid mass of partially digested food that leaves the stomach?",
        "Option1": "Bolus",
        "Option2": "Chyme",
        "Option3": "Feces",
        "Option4": "Bile",
        "Answer": "Chyme"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 38,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a type of sugar that cannot be digested by humans?",
        "Option1": "Glucose",
        "Option2": "Lactose",
        "Option3": "Sucrose",
        "Option4": "Fiber",
        "Answer": "Fiber"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 39,
        "Question": "What is the function of the appendix?",
        "Option1": "Digesting cellulose",
        "Option2": "Filtering blood",
        "Option3": "Its function in humans is not fully understood, but it is thought to play a role in the immune system",
        "Option4": "Producing digestive enzymes",
        "Answer": "Its function in humans is not fully understood, but it is thought to play a role in the immune system"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 40,
        "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a good source of complex carbohydrates?",
        "Option1": "Table sugar",
        "Option2": "White bread",
        "Option3": "Brown rice",
        "Option4": "Candy",
        "Answer": "Brown rice"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 41,
        "Question": "What is the term for a nutrient that the body cannot produce on its own and must be obtained from the diet?",
        "Option1": "Non-essential nutrient",
        "Option2": "Essential nutrient",
        "Option3": "Micronutrient",
        "Option4": "Macronutrient",
        "Answer": "Essential nutrient"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 42,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a key mineral for strong bones and teeth?",
        "Option1": "Iron",
        "Option2": "Calcium",
        "Option3": "Potassium",
        "Option4": "Sodium",
        "Answer": "Calcium"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 43,
        "Question": "What is the name of the condition caused by a lack of Vitamin C?",
        "Option1": "Rickets",
        "Option2": "Scurvy",
        "Option3": "Anemia",
        "Option4": "Night blindness",
        "Answer": "Scurvy"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 44,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a type of fatty acid that is considered 'healthy' and is found in avocados and nuts?",
        "Option1": "Saturated fat",
        "Option2": "Trans fat",
        "Option3": "Monounsaturated fat",
        "Option4": "Cholesterol",
        "Answer": "Monounsaturated fat"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 45,
        "Question": "What is the process of breaking down large food particles into smaller ones in the mouth called?",
        "Option1": "Peristalsis",
        "Option2": "Absorption",
        "Option3": "Mastication",
        "Option4": "Digestion",
        "Answer": "Mastication"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 46,
        "Question": "The small intestine is approximately how long in an adult human?",
        "Option1": "2-3 meters",
        "Option2": "6-7 meters",
        "Option3": "10-12 meters",
        "Option4": "15-20 meters",
        "Answer": "6-7 meters"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 47,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a function of the large intestine?",
        "Option1": "Secreting digestive enzymes",
        "Option2": "Breaking down fats",
        "Option3": "Housing beneficial bacteria that produce vitamins",
        "Option4": "Beginning the digestion of carbohydrates",
        "Answer": "Housing beneficial bacteria that produce vitamins"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 48,
        "Question": "What is the primary function of the stomach's rugae?",
        "Option1": "Increasing the surface area for absorption",
        "Option2": "Allowing the stomach to expand to hold food",
        "Option3": "Producing mucus",
        "Option4": "Filtering bacteria",
        "Answer": "Allowing the stomach to expand to hold food"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 49,
        "Question": "Which hormone is responsible for stimulating the release of bile from the gallbladder?",
        "Option1": "Gastrin",
        "Option2": "Insulin",
        "Option3": "Cholecystokinin (CCK)",
        "Option4": "Glucagon",
        "Answer": "Cholecystokinin (CCK)"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 50,
        "Question": "The process of absorbing nutrients into the bloodstream is called:",
        "Option1": "Digestion",
        "Option2": "Absorption",
        "Option3": "Elimination",
        "Option4": "Metabolism",
        "Answer": "Absorption"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 51,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a monosaccharide?",
        "Option1": "Sucrose",
        "Option2": "Maltose",
        "Option3": "Lactose",
        "Option4": "Glucose",
        "Answer": "Glucose"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 52,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a disaccharide?",
        "Option1": "Fructose",
        "Option2": "Galactose",
        "Option3": "Sucrose",
        "Option4": "Starch",
        "Answer": "Sucrose"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 53,
        "Question": "What is the term for a sugar that is made up of many glucose units linked together?",
        "Option1": "Monosaccharide",
        "Option2": "Disaccharide",
        "Option3": "Oligosaccharide",
        "Option4": "Polysaccharide",
        "Answer": "Polysaccharide"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 54,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a type of soluble fiber found in oats and legumes?",
        "Option1": "Cellulose",
        "Option2": "Hemicellulose",
        "Option3": "Pectin",
        "Option4": "Lignin",
        "Answer": "Pectin"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 55,
        "Question": "What is the name of the enzyme that digests fats in the small intestine?",
        "Option1": "Amylase",
        "Option2": "Pepsin",
        "Option3": "Lipase",
        "Option4": "Trypsin",
        "Answer": "Lipase"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 56,
        "Question": "The lymphatic system plays a crucial role in the absorption of:",
        "Option1": "Carbohydrates",
        "Option2": "Proteins",
        "Option3": "Fats",
        "Option4": "Water",
        "Answer": "Fats"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 57,
        "Question": "What is the name of the condition characterized by a deficiency of iron?",
        "Option1": "Anemia",
        "Option2": "Goiter",
        "Option3": "Osteoporosis",
        "Option4": "Rickets",
        "Answer": "Anemia"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 58,
        "Question": "Which of the following is an example of an incomplete protein?",
        "Option1": "Soybeans",
        "Option2": "Meat",
        "Option3": "Dairy products",
        "Option4": "Legumes",
        "Answer": "Legumes"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 59,
        "Question": "What is the role of the enzyme trypsin?",
        "Option1": "Digesting carbohydrates",
        "Option2": "Breaking down proteins in the small intestine",
        "Option3": "Emulsifying fats",
        "Option4": "Digesting nucleic acids",
        "Answer": "Breaking down proteins in the small intestine"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 60,
        "Question": "Which of the following vitamins is produced by bacteria in the large intestine?",
        "Option1": "Vitamin C",
        "Option2": "Vitamin B1",
        "Option3": "Vitamin K",
        "Option4": "Vitamin A",
        "Answer": "Vitamin K"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 61,
        "Question": "The condition known as 'lactose intolerance' is caused by a deficiency of which enzyme?",
        "Option1": "Amylase",
        "Option2": "Lipase",
        "Option3": "Lactase",
        "Option4": "Sucrase",
        "Answer": "Lactase"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 62,
        "Question": "Which part of the digestive system is responsible for producing the hormone insulin?",
        "Option1": "Stomach",
        "Option2": "Liver",
        "Option3": "Pancreas",
        "Option4": "Small intestine",
        "Answer": "Pancreas"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 63,
        "Question": "What is the function of the bile salts that emulsify fats?",
        "Option1": "They chemically break down fats",
        "Option2": "They increase the surface area of fat droplets for enzymes to act on",
        "Option3": "They absorb fats directly into the bloodstream",
        "Option4": "They prevent fats from being digested",
        "Answer": "They increase the surface area of fat droplets for enzymes to act on"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 64,
        "Question": "The lining of the small intestine is folded into structures called:",
        "Option1": "Rugae",
        "Option2": "Haustra",
        "Option3": "Villi and microvilli",
        "Option4": "Lacteals",
        "Answer": "Villi and microvilli"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 65,
        "Question": "What is the term for the wave-like muscle contractions that occur in the esophagus?",
        "Option1": "Mastication",
        "Option2": "Peristalsis",
        "Option3": "Deglutition",
        "Option4": "Churning",
        "Answer": "Peristalsis"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 66,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a good source of Vitamin A?",
        "Option1": "Citrus fruits",
        "Option2": "Dairy products and leafy green vegetables",
        "Option3": "Whole grains",
        "Option4": "Legumes",
        "Answer": "Dairy products and leafy green vegetables"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 67,
        "Question": "What is the main function of the enzyme salivary amylase?",
        "Option1": "Digesting proteins",
        "Option2": "Breaking down starches into simpler sugars",
        "Option3": "Breaking down fats",
        "Option4": "Activating other enzymes",
        "Answer": "Breaking down starches into simpler sugars"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 68,
        "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a macronutrient?",
        "Option1": "Vitamins",
        "Option2": "Minerals",
        "Option3": "Carbohydrates",
        "Option4": "Water",
        "Answer": "Carbohydrates"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 69,
        "Question": "The process of chewing food is also known as:",
        "Option1": "Deglutition",
        "Option2": "Ingestion",
        "Option3": "Mastication",
        "Option4": "Peristalsis",
        "Answer": "Mastication"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 70,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a key function of the liver in digestion?",
        "Option1": "Producing digestive enzymes for the small intestine",
        "Option2": "Storing bile",
        "Option3": "Producing bile",
        "Option4": "Absorbing water and electrolytes",
        "Answer": "Producing bile"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 71,
        "Question": "What is the name of the muscular tube that connects the pharynx to the stomach?",
        "Option1": "Trachea",
        "Option2": "Esophagus",
        "Option3": "Duodenum",
        "Option4": "Jejunum",
        "Answer": "Esophagus"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 72,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a type of fat that is solid at room temperature?",
        "Option1": "Unsaturated fat",
        "Option2": "Saturated fat",
        "Option3": "Trans fat",
        "Option4": "Monounsaturated fat",
        "Answer": "Saturated fat"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 73,
        "Question": "What is the term for a substance that helps to soften food and lubricate the mouth for swallowing?",
        "Option1": "Hydrochloric acid",
        "Option2": "Bile",
        "Option3": "Saliva",
        "Option4": "Mucus",
        "Answer": "Saliva"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 74,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a health benefit of dietary fiber?",
        "Option1": "Provides a large amount of energy",
        "Option2": "Helps regulate blood sugar levels and promotes bowel regularity",
        "Option3": "Is a key component of muscle tissue",
        "Option4": "Increases the absorption of fat",
        "Answer": "Helps regulate blood sugar levels and promotes bowel regularity"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 75,
        "Question": "What is the name of the digestive disorder characterized by the inflammation of the lining of the stomach?",
        "Option1": "Gastritis",
        "Option2": "Ulcer",
        "Option3": "Appendicitis",
        "Option4": "Celiac disease",
        "Answer": "Gastritis"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 76,
        "Question": "The pancreas secretes a substance that neutralizes the stomach acid in the small intestine. What is it?",
        "Option1": "Pepsin",
        "Option2": "Bile",
        "Option3": "Bicarbonate",
        "Option4": "Hydrochloric acid",
        "Answer": "Bicarbonate"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 77,
        "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a complete protein source?",
        "Option1": "Rice",
        "Option2": "Beans",
        "Option3": "Eggs",
        "Option4": "Corn",
        "Answer": "Eggs"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 78,
        "Question": "What is the recommended daily percentage of calories from fats?",
        "Option1": "Less than 10%",
        "Option2": "10-15%",
        "Option3": "20-35%",
        "Option4": "50-60%",
        "Answer": "20-35%"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 79,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a trace mineral?",
        "Option1": "Calcium",
        "Option2": "Potassium",
        "Option3": "Iron",
        "Option4": "Sodium",
        "Answer": "Iron"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 80,
        "Question": "The process of a nutrient being transported from the intestinal lumen into the blood or lymphatic system is called:",
        "Option1": "Digestion",
        "Option2": "Assimilation",
        "Option3": "Absorption",
        "Option4": "Excretion",
        "Answer": "Absorption"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 81,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a type of simple carbohydrate?",
        "Option1": "Starch",
        "Option2": "Cellulose",
        "Option3": "Fructose",
        "Option4": "Glycogen",
        "Answer": "Fructose"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 82,
        "Question": "What is the name of the sphincter that controls the flow of food from the esophagus to the stomach?",
        "Option1": "Pyloric sphincter",
        "Option2": "Cardiac sphincter",
        "Option3": "Ileocecal valve",
        "Option4": "Anal sphincter",
        "Answer": "Cardiac sphincter"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 83,
        "Question": "Which of the following vitamins is synthesized by the skin upon exposure to sunlight?",
        "Option1": "Vitamin C",
        "Option2": "Vitamin D",
        "Option3": "Vitamin E",
        "Option4": "Vitamin K",
        "Answer": "Vitamin D"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 84,
        "Question": "What is the role of the enzyme lactase?",
        "Option1": "Breaking down starch",
        "Option2": "Breaking down milk sugar (lactose)",
        "Option3": "Breaking down proteins",
        "Option4": "Breaking down fats",
        "Answer": "Breaking down milk sugar (lactose)"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 85,
        "Question": "The process of taking food into the body is called:",
        "Option1": "Digestion",
        "Option2": "Ingestion",
        "Option3": "Absorption",
        "Option4": "Elimination",
        "Answer": "Ingestion"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 86,
        "Question": "Which of the following is an essential fatty acid?",
        "Option1": "Saturated fat",
        "Option2": "Trans fat",
        "Option3": "Omega-3 fatty acid",
        "Option4": "Cholesterol",
        "Answer": "Omega-3 fatty acid"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 87,
        "Question": "What is the term for a measurement of the energy content of food?",
        "Option1": "Calorie",
        "Option2": "Gram",
        "Option3": "Milliliter",
        "Option4": "Joule",
        "Answer": "Calorie"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 88,
        "Question": "The breakdown of food into small particles by chewing is known as:",
        "Option1": "Chemical digestion",
        "Option2": "Mechanical digestion",
        "Option3": "Assimilation",
        "Option4": "Peristalsis",
        "Answer": "Mechanical digestion"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 89,
        "Question": "Which organ secretes glucagon, a hormone that raises blood sugar levels?",
        "Option1": "Liver",
        "Option2": "Stomach",
        "Option3": "Pancreas",
        "Option4": "Gallbladder",
        "Answer": "Pancreas"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 90,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a function of the appendix?",
        "Option1": "Storing bile",
        "Option2": "Producing digestive enzymes",
        "Option3": "Housing beneficial bacteria",
        "Option4": "No known function in humans",
        "Answer": "Housing beneficial bacteria"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 91,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a common cause of heartburn?",
        "Option1": "Bile reflux",
        "Option2": "Stomach acid flowing back into the esophagus",
        "Option3": "Lack of stomach acid",
        "Option4": "Excessive production of bile",
        "Answer": "Stomach acid flowing back into the esophagus"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 92,
        "Question": "What is the name of the condition caused by a lack of Vitamin D?",
        "Option1": "Scurvy",
        "Option2": "Beriberi",
        "Option3": "Rickets",
        "Option4": "Anemia",
        "Answer": "Rickets"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 93,
        "Question": "The process of converting food into energy is called:",
        "Option1": "Digestion",
        "Option2": "Metabolism",
        "Option3": "Absorption",
        "Option4": "Elimination",
        "Answer": "Metabolism"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 94,
        "Question": "What is the term for the process of eliminating undigested food from the body?",
        "Option1": "Ingestion",
        "Option2": "Absorption",
        "Option3": "Assimilation",
        "Option4": "Defecation",
        "Answer": "Defecation"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 95,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a structural protein found in skin, hair, and nails?",
        "Option1": "Enzyme",
        "Option2": "Hormone",
        "Option3": "Keratin",
        "Option4": "Antibody",
        "Answer": "Keratin"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 96,
        "Question": "What is the main function of the enzyme sucrase?",
        "Option1": "Breaking down fat",
        "Option2": "Breaking down proteins",
        "Option3": "Breaking down sucrose into glucose and fructose",
        "Option4": "Breaking down starch",
        "Answer": "Breaking down sucrose into glucose and fructose"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 97,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a major function of the kidneys?",
        "Option1": "Producing bile",
        "Option2": "Filtering waste products from the blood",
        "Option3": "Digesting carbohydrates",
        "Option4": "Absorbing nutrients",
        "Answer": "Filtering waste products from the blood"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 98,
        "Question": "What is the name of the muscle that controls the opening and closing of the anus?",
        "Option1": "Cardiac sphincter",
        "Option2": "Pyloric sphincter",
        "Option3": "Ileocecal valve",
        "Option4": "Anal sphincter",
        "Answer": "Anal sphincter"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 99,
        "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a mineral that is essential for proper thyroid function?",
        "Option1": "Iron",
        "Option2": "Calcium",
        "Option3": "Iodine",
        "Option4": "Zinc",
        "Answer": "Iodine"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 100,
        "Question": "What is the term for the process of adding hydrogen to liquid fats to make them solid at room temperature?",
        "Option1": "Emulsification",
        "Option2": "Hydrogenation",
        "Option3": "Digestion",
        "Option4": "Absorption",
        "Answer": "Hydrogenation"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 101,
        "Question": "Which of the following is NOT a major nutrient group?",
        "Option1": "Carbohydrates",
        "Option2": "Fats",
        "Option3": "Vitamins",
        "Option4": "Fiber",
        "Answer": "Fiber"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 102,
        "Question": "What is the primary role of carbohydrates in the body?",
        "Option1": "Building muscle tissue",
        "Option2": "Providing long-term energy storage",
        "Option3": "Acting as the body's main source of energy",
        "Option4": "Regulating body temperature",
        "Answer": "Acting as the body's main source of energy"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 103,
        "Question": "Which nutrient is essential for growth, repair, and maintenance of body tissues?",
        "Option1": "Carbohydrates",
        "Option2": "Proteins",
        "Option3": "Fats",
        "Option4": "Vitamins",
        "Answer": "Proteins"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 104,
        "Question": "What is the recommended daily intake of water for an average adult?",
        "Option1": "1-2 liters",
        "Option2": "2-3 liters",
        "Option3": "3-4 liters",
        "Option4": "More than 4 liters",
        "Answer": "2-3 liters"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 105,
        "Question": "Which of the following vitamins is fat-soluble?",
        "Option1": "Vitamin C",
        "Option2": "Vitamin B12",
        "Option3": "Vitamin K",
        "Option4": "Folic acid",
        "Answer": "Vitamin K"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 106,
        "Question": "The main function of the digestive system is to:",
        "Option1": "Filter waste products from the blood",
        "Option2": "Break down food into smaller molecules for absorption",
        "Option3": "Produce hormones for body regulation",
        "Option4": "Transport oxygen to the body's cells",
        "Answer": "Break down food into smaller molecules for absorption"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 107,
        "Question": "Digestion of carbohydrates begins in the:",
        "Option1": "Stomach",
        "Option2": "Small intestine",
        "Option3": "Mouth",
        "Option4": "Esophagus",
        "Answer": "Mouth"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 108,
        "Question": "What is the name of the enzyme in saliva that begins the digestion of starches?",
        "Option1": "Pepsin",
        "Option2": "Amylase",
        "Option3": "Lipase",
        "Option4": "Trypsin",
        "Answer": "Amylase"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 109,
        "Question": "The wave-like muscle contractions that move food through the digestive tract are called:",
        "Option1": "Absorption",
        "Option2": "Peristalsis",
        "Option3": "Segmentation",
        "Option4": "Mastication",
        "Answer": "Peristalsis"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 110,
        "Question": "The stomach's lining is protected from its own acid by:",
        "Option1": "Villi",
        "Option2": "Mucus",
        "Option3": "Bile",
        "Option4": "Saliva",
        "Answer": "Mucus"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 111,
        "Question": "Which enzyme in the stomach is responsible for beginning the digestion of proteins?",
        "Option1": "Amylase",
        "Option2": "Lipase",
        "Option3": "Pepsin",
        "Option4": "Trypsin",
        "Answer": "Pepsin"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 112,
        "Question": "The majority of nutrient absorption occurs in the:",
        "Option1": "Stomach",
        "Option2": "Large intestine",
        "Option3": "Small intestine",
        "Option4": "Esophagus",
        "Answer": "Small intestine"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 113,
        "Question": "The finger-like projections that line the small intestine and increase the surface area for absorption are called:",
        "Option1": "Rugae",
        "Option2": "Villi",
        "Option3": "Pyloric sphincters",
        "Option4": "Haustra",
        "Answer": "Villi"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 114,
        "Question": "What is the role of bile in digestion?",
        "Option1": "Digesting proteins",
        "Option2": "Emulsifying fats",
        "Option3": "Absorbing water",
        "Option4": "Breaking down carbohydrates",
        "Answer": "Emulsifying fats"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 115,
        "Question": "Which organ produces bile?",
        "Option1": "Gallbladder",
        "Option2": "Pancreas",
        "Option3": "Stomach",
        "Option4": "Liver",
        "Answer": "Liver"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 116,
        "Question": "The pancreas secretes which of the following digestive enzymes?",
        "Option1": "Pepsin",
        "Option2": "Amylase",
        "Option3": "Lipase",
        "Option4": "All of the above",
        "Answer": "All of the above"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 117,
        "Question": "What is the primary function of the large intestine?",
        "Option1": "Breaking down proteins",
        "Option2": "Absorbing water and electrolytes",
        "Option3": "Digesting fats",
        "Option4": "Producing digestive enzymes",
        "Answer": "Absorbing water and electrolytes"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 118,
        "Question": "Where is undigested food stored before it is eliminated from the body?",
        "Option1": "Small intestine",
        "Option2": "Stomach",
        "Option3": "Rectum",
        "Option4": "Liver",
        "Answer": "Rectum"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 119,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a water-soluble vitamin?",
        "Option1": "Vitamin A",
        "Option2": "Vitamin D",
        "Option3": "Vitamin C",
        "Option4": "Vitamin E",
        "Answer": "Vitamin C"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 120,
        "Question": "What is the function of the gallbladder?",
        "Option1": "Produce bile",
        "Option2": "Store and concentrate bile",
        "Option3": "Produce digestive enzymes",
        "Option4": "Absorb nutrients",
        "Answer": "Store and concentrate bile"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 121,
        "Question": "The breakdown of food by chewing and mixing is a form of:",
        "Option1": "Chemical digestion",
        "Option2": "Mechanical digestion",
        "Option3": "Absorption",
        "Option4": "Elimination",
        "Answer": "Mechanical digestion"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 122,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a key function of proteins?",
        "Option1": "Energy storage",
        "Option2": "Insulation",
        "Option3": "Enzyme and hormone production",
        "Option4": "Primary energy source",
        "Answer": "Enzyme and hormone production"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 123,
        "Question": "Which organ is responsible for detoxifying harmful substances and producing blood proteins?",
        "Option1": "Pancreas",
        "Option2": "Stomach",
        "Option3": "Liver",
        "Option4": "Kidneys",
        "Answer": "Liver"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 124,
        "Question": "The small intestine is divided into three sections. What are they in order?",
        "Option1": "Jejunum, ileum, duodenum",
        "Option2": "Duodenum, jejunum, ileum",
        "Option3": "Ileum, duodenum, jejunum",
        "Option4": "Duodenum, ileum, jejunum",
        "Answer": "Duodenum, jejunum, ileum"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 125,
        "Question": "What is the name of the sphincter that separates the stomach from the small intestine?",
        "Option1": "Cardiac sphincter",
        "Option2": "Pyloric sphincter",
        "Option3": "Anal sphincter",
        "Option4": "Esophageal sphincter",
        "Answer": "Pyloric sphincter"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 126,
        "Question": "The breakdown of food molecules using enzymes is a form of:",
        "Option1": "Mechanical digestion",
        "Option2": "Chemical digestion",
        "Option3": "Absorption",
        "Option4": "Peristalsis",
        "Answer": "Chemical digestion"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 127,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a micronutrient?",
        "Option1": "Carbohydrates",
        "Option2": "Fats",
        "Option3": "Minerals",
        "Option4": "Proteins",
        "Answer": "Minerals"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 128,
        "Question": "What is the main function of the epiglottis?",
        "Option1": "Producing saliva",
        "Option2": "Preventing food from entering the trachea",
        "Option3": "Breaking down starches",
        "Option4": "Storing bile",
        "Answer": "Preventing food from entering the trachea"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 129,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a type of protein that speeds up chemical reactions in the body?",
        "Option1": "Hormones",
        "Option2": "Enzymes",
        "Option3": "Antibodies",
        "Option4": "Collagen",
        "Answer": "Enzymes"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 130,
        "Question": "Where are most of the digestive enzymes produced?",
        "Option1": "Stomach and liver",
        "Option2": "Mouth and esophagus",
        "Option3": "Pancreas and small intestine",
        "Option4": "Gallbladder and large intestine",
        "Answer": "Pancreas and small intestine"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 131,
        "Question": "The process of moving food from the mouth to the stomach is called:",
        "Option1": "Peristalsis",
        "Option2": "Deglutition (swallowing)",
        "Option3": "Mastication",
        "Option4": "Absorption",
        "Answer": "Deglutition (swallowing)"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 132,
        "Question": "What is the function of the hydrochloric acid in the stomach?",
        "Option1": "Neutralizing stomach acid",
        "Option2": "Activating pepsinogen and killing bacteria",
        "Option3": "Emulsifying fats",
        "Option4": "Digesting carbohydrates",
        "Answer": "Activating pepsinogen and killing bacteria"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 133,
        "Question": "Which nutrient provides the highest energy density (calories per gram)?",
        "Option1": "Proteins",
        "Option2": "Carbohydrates",
        "Option3": "Fats",
        "Option4": "Vitamins",
        "Answer": "Fats"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 134,
        "Question": "The end products of carbohydrate digestion are:",
        "Option1": "Amino acids",
        "Option2": "Fatty acids and glycerol",
        "Option3": "Monosaccharides (simple sugars)",
        "Option4": "Nucleotides",
        "Answer": "Monosaccharides (simple sugars)"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 135,
        "Question": "The end products of protein digestion are:",
        "Option1": "Amino acids",
        "Option2": "Fatty acids and glycerol",
        "Option3": "Monosaccharides (simple sugars)",
        "Option4": "Nucleotides",
        "Answer": "Amino acids"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 136,
        "Question": "The end products of fat digestion are:",
        "Option1": "Amino acids",
        "Option2": "Fatty acids and glycerol",
        "Option3": "Monosaccharides (simple sugars)",
        "Option4": "Nucleotides",
        "Answer": "Fatty acids and glycerol"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 137,
        "Question": "What is the name of the semi-liquid mass of partially digested food that leaves the stomach?",
        "Option1": "Bolus",
        "Option2": "Chyme",
        "Option3": "Feces",
        "Option4": "Bile",
        "Answer": "Chyme"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 138,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a type of sugar that cannot be digested by humans?",
        "Option1": "Glucose",
        "Option2": "Lactose",
        "Option3": "Sucrose",
        "Option4": "Fiber",
        "Answer": "Fiber"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 139,
        "Question": "What is the function of the appendix?",
        "Option1": "Digesting cellulose",
        "Option2": "Filtering blood",
        "Option3": "Its function in humans is not fully understood, but it is thought to play a role in the immune system",
        "Option4": "Producing digestive enzymes",
        "Answer": "Its function in humans is not fully understood, but it is thought to play a role in the immune system"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 140,
        "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a good source of complex carbohydrates?",
        "Option1": "Table sugar",
        "Option2": "White bread",
        "Option3": "Brown rice",
        "Option4": "Candy",
        "Answer": "Brown rice"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 141,
        "Question": "What is the term for a nutrient that the body cannot produce on its own and must be obtained from the diet?",
        "Option1": "Non-essential nutrient",
        "Option2": "Essential nutrient",
        "Option3": "Micronutrient",
        "Option4": "Macronutrient",
        "Answer": "Essential nutrient"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 142,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a key mineral for strong bones and teeth?",
        "Option1": "Iron",
        "Option2": "Calcium",
        "Option3": "Potassium",
        "Option4": "Sodium",
        "Answer": "Calcium"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 143,
        "Question": "What is the name of the condition caused by a lack of Vitamin C?",
        "Option1": "Rickets",
        "Option2": "Scurvy",
        "Option3": "Anemia",
        "Option4": "Night blindness",
        "Answer": "Scurvy"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 144,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a type of fatty acid that is considered 'healthy' and is found in avocados and nuts?",
        "Option1": "Saturated fat",
        "Option2": "Trans fat",
        "Option3": "Monounsaturated fat",
        "Option4": "Cholesterol",
        "Answer": "Monounsaturated fat"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 145,
        "Question": "What is the process of breaking down large food particles into smaller ones in the mouth called?",
        "Option1": "Peristalsis",
        "Option2": "Absorption",
        "Option3": "Mastication",
        "Option4": "Digestion",
        "Answer": "Mastication"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 146,
        "Question": "The small intestine is approximately how long in an adult human?",
        "Option1": "2-3 meters",
        "Option2": "6-7 meters",
        "Option3": "10-12 meters",
        "Option4": "15-20 meters",
        "Answer": "6-7 meters"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 147,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a function of the large intestine?",
        "Option1": "Secreting digestive enzymes",
        "Option2": "Breaking down fats",
        "Option3": "Housing beneficial bacteria that produce vitamins",
        "Option4": "Beginning the digestion of carbohydrates",
        "Answer": "Housing beneficial bacteria that produce vitamins"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 148,
        "Question": "What is the primary function of the stomach's rugae?",
        "Option1": "Increasing the surface area for absorption",
        "Option2": "Allowing the stomach to expand to hold food",
        "Option3": "Producing mucus",
        "Option4": "Filtering bacteria",
        "Answer": "Allowing the stomach to expand to hold food"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 149,
        "Question": "Which hormone is responsible for stimulating the release of bile from the gallbladder?",
        "Option1": "Gastrin",
        "Option2": "Insulin",
        "Option3": "Cholecystokinin (CCK)",
        "Option4": "Glucagon",
        "Answer": "Cholecystokinin (CCK)"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 150,
        "Question": "The process of absorbing nutrients into the bloodstream is called:",
        "Option1": "Digestion",
        "Option2": "Absorption",
        "Option3": "Elimination",
        "Option4": "Metabolism",
        "Answer": "Absorption"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 151,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a monosaccharide?",
        "Option1": "Sucrose",
        "Option2": "Maltose",
        "Option3": "Lactose",
        "Option4": "Glucose",
        "Answer": "Glucose"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 152,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a disaccharide?",
        "Option1": "Fructose",
        "Option2": "Galactose",
        "Option3": "Sucrose",
        "Option4": "Starch",
        "Answer": "Sucrose"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 153,
        "Question": "What is the term for a sugar that is made up of many glucose units linked together?",
        "Option1": "Monosaccharide",
        "Option2": "Disaccharide",
        "Option3": "Oligosaccharide",
        "Option4": "Polysaccharide",
        "Answer": "Polysaccharide"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 154,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a type of soluble fiber found in oats and legumes?",
        "Option1": "Cellulose",
        "Option2": "Hemicellulose",
        "Option3": "Pectin",
        "Option4": "Lignin",
        "Answer": "Pectin"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 155,
        "Question": "What is the name of the enzyme that digests fats in the small intestine?",
        "Option1": "Amylase",
        "Option2": "Pepsin",
        "Option3": "Lipase",
        "Option4": "Trypsin",
        "Answer": "Lipase"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 156,
        "Question": "The lymphatic system plays a crucial role in the absorption of:",
        "Option1": "Carbohydrates",
        "Option2": "Proteins",
        "Option3": "Fats",
        "Option4": "Water",
        "Answer": "Fats"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 157,
        "Question": "What is the name of the condition characterized by a deficiency of iron?",
        "Option1": "Anemia",
        "Option2": "Goiter",
        "Option3": "Osteoporosis",
        "Option4": "Rickets",
        "Answer": "Anemia"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 158,
        "Question": "Which of the following is an example of an incomplete protein?",
        "Option1": "Soybeans",
        "Option2": "Meat",
        "Option3": "Dairy products",
        "Option4": "Legumes",
        "Answer": "Legumes"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 159,
        "Question": "What is the role of the enzyme trypsin?",
        "Option1": "Digesting carbohydrates",
        "Option2": "Breaking down proteins in the small intestine",
        "Option3": "Emulsifying fats",
        "Option4": "Digesting nucleic acids",
        "Answer": "Breaking down proteins in the small intestine"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 160,
        "Question": "Which of the following vitamins is produced by bacteria in the large intestine?",
        "Option1": "Vitamin C",
        "Option2": "Vitamin B1",
        "Option3": "Vitamin K",
        "Option4": "Vitamin A",
        "Answer": "Vitamin K"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 161,
        "Question": "The condition known as 'lactose intolerance' is caused by a deficiency of which enzyme?",
        "Option1": "Amylase",
        "Option2": "Lipase",
        "Option3": "Lactase",
        "Option4": "Sucrase",
        "Answer": "Lactase"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 162,
        "Question": "Which part of the digestive system is responsible for producing the hormone insulin?",
        "Option1": "Stomach",
        "Option2": "Liver",
        "Option3": "Pancreas",
        "Option4": "Small intestine",
        "Answer": "Pancreas"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 163,
        "Question": "What is the function of the bile salts that emulsify fats?",
        "Option1": "They chemically break down fats",
        "Option2": "They increase the surface area of fat droplets for enzymes to act on",
        "Option3": "They absorb fats directly into the bloodstream",
        "Option4": "They prevent fats from being digested",
        "Answer": "They increase the surface area of fat droplets for enzymes to act on"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 164,
        "Question": "The lining of the small intestine is folded into structures called:",
        "Option1": "Rugae",
        "Option2": "Haustra",
        "Option3": "Villi and microvilli",
        "Option4": "Lacteals",
        "Answer": "Villi and microvilli"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 165,
        "Question": "What is the term for the wave-like muscle contractions that occur in the esophagus?",
        "Option1": "Mastication",
        "Option2": "Peristalsis",
        "Option3": "Deglutition",
        "Option4": "Churning",
        "Answer": "Peristalsis"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 166,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a good source of Vitamin A?",
        "Option1": "Citrus fruits",
        "Option2": "Dairy products and leafy green vegetables",
        "Option3": "Whole grains",
        "Option4": "Legumes",
        "Answer": "Dairy products and leafy green vegetables"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 167,
        "Question": "What is the main function of the enzyme salivary amylase?",
        "Option1": "Digesting proteins",
        "Option2": "Breaking down starches into simpler sugars",
        "Option3": "Breaking down fats",
        "Option4": "Activating other enzymes",
        "Answer": "Breaking down starches into simpler sugars"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 168,
        "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a macronutrient?",
        "Option1": "Vitamins",
        "Option2": "Minerals",
        "Option3": "Carbohydrates",
        "Option4": "Water",
        "Answer": "Carbohydrates"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 169,
        "Question": "The process of chewing food is also known as:",
        "Option1": "Deglutition",
        "Option2": "Ingestion",
        "Option3": "Mastication",
        "Option4": "Peristalsis",
        "Answer": "Mastication"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 170,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a key function of the liver in digestion?",
        "Option1": "Producing digestive enzymes for the small intestine",
        "Option2": "Storing bile",
        "Option3": "Producing bile",
        "Option4": "Absorbing water and electrolytes",
        "Answer": "Producing bile"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 171,
        "Question": "What is the name of the muscular tube that connects the pharynx to the stomach?",
        "Option1": "Trachea",
        "Option2": "Esophagus",
        "Option3": "Duodenum",
        "Option4": "Jejunum",
        "Answer": "Esophagus"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 172,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a type of fat that is solid at room temperature?",
        "Option1": "Unsaturated fat",
        "Option2": "Saturated fat",
        "Option3": "Trans fat",
        "Option4": "Monounsaturated fat",
        "Answer": "Saturated fat"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 173,
        "Question": "What is the term for a substance that helps to soften food and lubricate the mouth for swallowing?",
        "Option1": "Hydrochloric acid",
        "Option2": "Bile",
        "Option3": "Saliva",
        "Option4": "Mucus",
        "Answer": "Saliva"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 174,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a health benefit of dietary fiber?",
        "Option1": "Provides a large amount of energy",
        "Option2": "Helps regulate blood sugar levels and promotes bowel regularity",
        "Option3": "Is a key component of muscle tissue",
        "Option4": "Increases the absorption of fat",
        "Answer": "Helps regulate blood sugar levels and promotes bowel regularity"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 175,
        "Question": "What is the name of the digestive disorder characterized by the inflammation of the lining of the stomach?",
        "Option1": "Gastritis",
        "Option2": "Ulcer",
        "Option3": "Appendicitis",
        "Option4": "Celiac disease",
        "Answer": "Gastritis"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 176,
        "Question": "The pancreas secretes a substance that neutralizes the stomach acid in the small intestine. What is it?",
        "Option1": "Pepsin",
        "Option2": "Bile",
        "Option3": "Bicarbonate",
        "Option4": "Hydrochloric acid",
        "Answer": "Bicarbonate"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 177,
        "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a complete protein source?",
        "Option1": "Rice",
        "Option2": "Beans",
        "Option3": "Eggs",
        "Option4": "Corn",
        "Answer": "Eggs"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 178,
        "Question": "What is the recommended daily percentage of calories from fats?",
        "Option1": "Less than 10%",
        "Option2": "10-15%",
        "Option3": "20-35%",
        "Option4": "50-60%",
        "Answer": "20-35%"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 179,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a trace mineral?",
        "Option1": "Calcium",
        "Option2": "Potassium",
        "Option3": "Iron",
        "Option4": "Sodium",
        "Answer": "Iron"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 180,
        "Question": "The process of a nutrient being transported from the intestinal lumen into the blood or lymphatic system is called:",
        "Option1": "Digestion",
        "Option2": "Assimilation",
        "Option3": "Absorption",
        "Option4": "Excretion",
        "Answer": "Absorption"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 181,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a type of simple carbohydrate?",
        "Option1": "Starch",
        "Option2": "Cellulose",
        "Option3": "Fructose",
        "Option4": "Glycogen",
        "Answer": "Fructose"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 182,
        "Question": "What is the name of the sphincter that controls the flow of food from the esophagus to the stomach?",
        "Option1": "Pyloric sphincter",
        "Option2": "Cardiac sphincter",
        "Option3": "Ileocecal valve",
        "Option4": "Anal sphincter",
        "Answer": "Cardiac sphincter"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 183,
        "Question": "Which of the following vitamins is synthesized by the skin upon exposure to sunlight?",
        "Option1": "Vitamin C",
        "Option2": "Vitamin D",
        "Option3": "Vitamin E",
        "Option4": "Vitamin K",
        "Answer": "Vitamin D"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 184,
        "Question": "What is the role of the enzyme lactase?",
        "Option1": "Breaking down starch",
        "Option2": "Breaking down milk sugar (lactose)",
        "Option3": "Breaking down proteins",
        "Option4": "Breaking down fats",
        "Answer": "Breaking down milk sugar (lactose)"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 185,
        "Question": "The process of taking food into the body is called:",
        "Option1": "Digestion",
        "Option2": "Ingestion",
        "Option3": "Absorption",
        "Option4": "Elimination",
        "Answer": "Ingestion"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 186,
        "Question": "Which of the following is an essential fatty acid?",
        "Option1": "Saturated fat",
        "Option2": "Trans fat",
        "Option3": "Omega-3 fatty acid",
        "Option4": "Cholesterol",
        "Answer": "Omega-3 fatty acid"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 187,
        "Question": "What is the term for a measurement of the energy content of food?",
        "Option1": "Calorie",
        "Option2": "Gram",
        "Option3": "Milliliter",
        "Option4": "Joule",
        "Answer": "Calorie"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 188,
        "Question": "The breakdown of food into small particles by chewing is known as:",
        "Option1": "Chemical digestion",
        "Option2": "Mechanical digestion",
        "Option3": "Assimilation",
        "Option4": "Peristalsis",
        "Answer": "Mechanical digestion"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 189,
        "Question": "Which organ secretes glucagon, a hormone that raises blood sugar levels?",
        "Option1": "Liver",
        "Option2": "Stomach",
        "Option3": "Pancreas",
        "Option4": "Gallbladder",
        "Answer": "Pancreas"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 190,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a function of the appendix?",
        "Option1": "Storing bile",
        "Option2": "Producing digestive enzymes",
        "Option3": "Housing beneficial bacteria",
        "Option4": "No known function in humans",
        "Answer": "Housing beneficial bacteria"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 191,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a common cause of heartburn?",
        "Option1": "Bile reflux",
        "Option2": "Stomach acid flowing back into the esophagus",
        "Option3": "Lack of stomach acid",
        "Option4": "Excessive production of bile",
        "Answer": "Stomach acid flowing back into the esophagus"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 192,
        "Question": "What is the name of the condition caused by a lack of Vitamin D?",
        "Option1": "Scurvy",
        "Option2": "Beriberi",
        "Option3": "Rickets",
        "Option4": "Anemia",
        "Answer": "Rickets"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 193,
        "Question": "The process of converting food into energy is called:",
        "Option1": "Digestion",
        "Option2": "Metabolism",
        "Option3": "Absorption",
        "Option4": "Elimination",
        "Answer": "Metabolism"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 194,
        "Question": "What is the term for the process of eliminating undigested food from the body?",
        "Option1": "Ingestion",
        "Option2": "Absorption",
        "Option3": "Assimilation",
        "Option4": "Defecation",
        "Answer": "Defecation"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 195,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a structural protein found in skin, hair, and nails?",
        "Option1": "Enzyme",
        "Option2": "Hormone",
        "Option3": "Keratin",
        "Option4": "Antibody",
        "Answer": "Keratin"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 196,
        "Question": "What is the main function of the enzyme sucrase?",
        "Option1": "Breaking down fat",
        "Option2": "Breaking down proteins",
        "Option3": "Breaking down sucrose into glucose and fructose",
        "Option4": "Breaking down starch",
        "Answer": "Breaking down sucrose into glucose and fructose"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 197,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a major function of the kidneys?",
        "Option1": "Producing bile",
        "Option2": "Filtering waste products from the blood",
        "Option3": "Digesting carbohydrates",
        "Option4": "Absorbing nutrients",
        "Answer": "Filtering waste products from the blood"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 198,
        "Question": "What is the name of the muscle that controls the opening and closing of the anus?",
        "Option1": "Cardiac sphincter",
        "Option2": "Pyloric sphincter",
        "Option3": "Ileocecal valve",
        "Option4": "Anal sphincter",
        "Answer": "Anal sphincter"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 199,
        "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a mineral that is essential for proper thyroid function?",
        "Option1": "Iron",
        "Option2": "Calcium",
        "Option3": "Iodine",
        "Option4": "Zinc",
        "Answer": "Iodine"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 200,
        "Question": "What is the term for the process of adding hydrogen to liquid fats to make them solid at room temperature?",
        "Option1": "Emulsification",
        "Option2": "Hydrogenation",
        "Option3": "Digestion",
        "Option4": "Absorption",
        "Answer": "Hydrogenation"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 201,
        "Question": "What is the term for the ring of muscle that separates the small intestine from the large intestine?",
        "Option1": "Pyloric sphincter",
        "Option2": "Cardiac sphincter",
        "Option3": "Ileocecal valve",
        "Option4": "Anal sphincter",
        "Answer": "Ileocecal valve"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 202,
        "Question": "What is the primary function of the nutrient fiber in the diet?",
        "Option1": "To provide energy",
        "Option2": "To build muscle tissue",
        "Option3": "To aid in digestion and prevent constipation",
        "Option4": "To absorb fat-soluble vitamins",
        "Answer": "To aid in digestion and prevent constipation"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 203,
        "Question": "Which of the following is the main function of the small intestine's microvilli?",
        "Option1": "Secreting digestive enzymes",
        "Option2": "Increasing the surface area for nutrient absorption",
        "Option3": "Producing hormones",
        "Option4": "Controlling the movement of food",
        "Answer": "Increasing the surface area for nutrient absorption"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 204,
        "Question": "What is the name of the digestive enzyme that breaks down proteins in the small intestine?",
        "Option1": "Pepsin",
        "Option2": "Trypsin",
        "Option3": "Amylase",
        "Option4": "Lipase",
        "Answer": "Trypsin"
      },
      {
        "question_no.": 205,
        "Question": "Which of the following is a health concern associated with excessive consumption of saturated fats?",
        "Option1": "Lactose intolerance",
        "Option2": "Increased risk of heart disease",
        "Option3": "Iron deficiency anemia",
        "Option4": "Vitamin C deficiency",
        "Answer": "Increased risk of heart disease"
      }
    ]